Guide to the Connecticut AIDS Action Council 1990-2002 GLBTQ.2011.01 GLBTQ.2011.01
GLBTQ Archives, Central Connecticut State University
Connecticut AIDS Action Council records
1990-2002
GLBTQ.2011.01
GLBTQ Archives, Central Connecticut State University
6.0 Linear feet
John Bonelli, a UCONN graduate, is a political activist and community organizer. In 1989 he ran openly gay for the Hartford City Council as the candidate of the People for Change coalition. For years he worked as an activist and consultant in several organizations related to HIV/AIDS issues and as an intern and volunteer in political campaigns. For years Mr. Bonelli was a state wide co-chairperson of the Connecticut AIDS Action Council. This collection consists of administrative records of the council.
Bonelli, John
Conditions Governing Access note
There are no restrictions on access to this collection.
Biographical Note
John Bonelli, MSW, graduated from the University of Connecticut School of Social Work in 1990. He has been a community organizer and political activist since his undergraduate years at Trinity College in Hartford. He ran as an openly gay, progressive candidate for Hartford City Council in 1989 as part of the People for Change (PFC) slate of candidates. People for Change, founded in 1987, was a progressive multicultural coalition and political party made up of labor unions, neighborhood activists and LGBT, Puerto Rican and African American communities and organizations. The coalition also included environmental, citizen and women's issues activists. PFC was successful in unseating members of the Republican minority party on the Hartford City Council in 1987, 1989 and 1991.
Mr. Bonelli was the statewide Co-chairperson of the CT Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights, a member of the Legislative Electoral Action Program, the Policy and Community Organizing Director for the CT Positive Action Coalition (HIV/AIDS issues) and a staff person, consultant, volunteer or intern for various electoral campaigns including those of CT State Representatives Juan Figueroa and Evelyn Mantilla, City Council persons Louise Simmons and Susan Hyde, and United States Senate candidate Ned Lamont, and other campaigns. He has been a campaign organizer, fundraiser and volunteer coordinator. Mr. Bonelli has been an adjunct faculty member and advisor at UConn and Hunter College Schools of Social Work. Presently, he works at the New York City based HIV prevention research group- Project ACHIEVE- as the recruitment and community relations coordinator and at the UCONN School of Social Work as a Field Education Coordinator.
The Connecticut AIDS Action Council (CAAC) was created as a statewide coalition of people living with HIV/AIDS, their families, supporters, and AIDS Service providers. They fought to provide assistance to people with HIV/AIDS as well as advocate and rally for policy issues regarding HIV/AIDS.
Arrangement note
The collection is arranged alphabetically.
Scope and Contents note
The Connecticut AIDS Action Council Collection consists of adminstrative records and subject files.
Oral History Interview
An oral history interview of John Bonelli is available within the Digital Collections of the GLTBQ Archives on the website of the Elihu Burritt Library.
Administrative records.; AIDS (Disease) -- Prevention.; AIDS (Disease) -- Social aspects.; AIDS activists; Archival Material; Article; Gay rights.; Homosexuality -- United States.; Lesbians -- United States.
- Administrative Records
  - Act-Up CT- Protests of Department of Public Health Commissioner's Move to Collect Names of People with HIV., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act) information, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ADAP (AIDS Drug Assistance Program)- Federal funding cutting back., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advocates for Connecticut's Children and Youth, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - African American HIV University- Schedule, learning objectives, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A.I.D. a Pet Tails- February periodical, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Action Council- Membership Info, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AIDS Action Council/Voting Record, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AIDS Action Council - Fiscal & legislative information on AIDS prevention and support funding, newsletter, 1996-2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Articles and testimonials, 1990-2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AIDS Awareness Day, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Awareness Day, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AIDS Awareness Day, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - AIDS Awareness Day, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AIDS Candlelight Vigil, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AIDS Community Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AIDS Cure Project (ACP)- Plan, articles, questions, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AIDS Data Reporting (Proposed bill)- Information, testimonials, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AIDS Education and Research Fund; tax check-off provision (for donating tax refund to AIDS research)., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AIDS Education For a Diverse Community - Hispanic Issues in AIDS Education- American Red Cross, November 11, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - AIDS Funding- Budgets cuts and the effects, newspaper articles, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - AIDS Legal Network, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - AIDS Ministries Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - AIDS Project Hartford- Women's Initiative Project; Funds Survey, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - AIDS Rally & Lobby Day- Flyer, information, Hartford, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - AIDS Reflection Event- Program and Flyer, Bristol, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - AIDS Statistics, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - AIDS/STD News Report (periodical), undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - AIDS Treatment News, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - AIDS Vaccine Effort- John Hopkins University, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - AIDS Watch- National Association of People with AIDS (NAPWA), 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - AIDS Watch- National Association of People with AIDS (NAPWA), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - AIDS Watch- National Association of People with AIDS (NAPWA), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - AIDS Week- National Minority AIDS Council (NMAC), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Alderwoman Nancy Ahern Needs HIV Education!! (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - AmFAR- American Foundation for AIDS Research - Letter of Intent for public policy grant, response, grant committee, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - APNH Newsline 1996, 1997 periodical AIDS Project New Haven (REMOVED) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - APRICOTS Restaurant Case- Newspaper articles, court documents, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - April 6th Reception - Fundraiser (Immaculate Reception Feast), April, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Artist Against AIDS- First Meeting (1994) agenda, events, funding requests, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - (Bad) Boy Next Door Tony Valenzuela performance, October 11, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Beagle, Terry- Funeral program, correspondence expressing condolences, newspaper articles, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Berkeley Federal Bank vs. Whitney Development Corp.- Connecticut Union of Disabilties Action Group (CUDAG) Amicus Brief w/Legal Assistance Resource Center of Connecticut (LARCC)., 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Betty Gallo & Company- Legislative Agenda, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Betty Gallo & Company- A Better Way Foundation- Legislative Report- Alternatives to incarceration, drug legislation, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Betty Gallo & Company- A Better Way Foundation Retreat- Agenda, notes, information on legislation to be discussed, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Block Grants Regional/State- Actions alerts, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield- Anthem Merger- Information, Petition, Building Parent Power Subcommittee meeting, newspaper articles, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bonelli, John G.- Run for Hartford City Council article, resume, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - CAAC- Action Alerts, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - CAAC- Board handouts- Director's Report, announcements, memos, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - CAAC- Board Member Agreement forms (signed and blank), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - CAAC- Board Minutes, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - CAAC- Board Structure and Responsibilities, other information, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - CAAC- Brochure planning, No date (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - CAAC- Funding requests and reports, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - CAAC- Grassroots network lobbying, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - CAAC- Incorporation Papers, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - CAAC- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - CAAC- Tax Exempt Status IRS Letter & Fed ID number for Grants, June 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - CAAC- Various meeting agendas and notes taken, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - CABHN- Connecticut Alliance for Basic Human Needs- Political issues i.e. welfare, homelessness, and condom use among adolescents, questions for candidates, 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - CABHN FEVER- Newsletters, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - CADAP (Connecticut AIDS Drug Assistance Program)- Announcement of new drugs added/covered in program, advisory committee meeting agendas, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - CADAP- Announcement of new drugs added/covered in program,funding requests, statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - CADAP- Legislation Revision, April, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - CADAP- Projection information for 1997, June, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Campaign endorsements and requests, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Candidates' Forum on HIV/AIDS- Agenda, attendance, questions, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - CARC (The Connecticut Aids Residence Coalition)- Standards of Care for people living with HIV in residential programs by Shawn Lang, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - CARC- 13th Annual Meeting, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Center for AIDS Prevention Studies, UCSF- Question and answer pamphlets, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research on AIDS (CIRA) - Community Advisory Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research in AIDS (CIRA)- Community Advisory Committee notes, meetings, 1997-1998; 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Center for Disease Control (CDC) - General, 1993; 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Center for Research & Public Policy- Newsletter, Statewide Consortia Membership memo; Needs assessment, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Alliance for Public Education- News Alerts membership letters, event information, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Citizens for Connecticut's Children and Youth- The Capital Corridor Project draft, notes, progress report, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Clean Water Action- Articles, updates (concern to CAAC due to higher risk of disease by contaminated water in the decreased immune systems of AIDS sufferers.), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Coalition For Democracy- Updates on local legislation, meeting minutes, flyers, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Community Foundation for Greater New Haven- Application for a grant from CAAC, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Community Works of Connecticut- Meeting minutes, correspondence, organization information, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Condoms in Schools & Sex Education- Articles, talking points, fact sheets, 1992-2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Confidentiality & Health Insurance - HIV Test, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Contact List, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut AIDS Bike Tour- Planning documents, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut AIDS Drug Assistance Program- Funding projections for 1998, Telephone Log, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut AIDS Education and Training Center- Correspondence & Connecticut AIDS Education Network (Red Cross) newsletter, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut AIDS Residence Coalition- Advocacy Agenda, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut AIDS Residence Coalition- Annual Report, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Connecticut AIDS Residence Coalition- "Creating Homes, Creating Hope: An AIDS Housing Conference", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut AIDS Residence Coalition- Emergency Housing Fund- Ryan White Title I and II, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut AIDS Residence Coalition- Member List/Board, membership directory, 1993, 1995, 1996, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Connecticut AIDS Residence Coalition- Shawn Lang Testimony to support Bill 6699: An Act Concerning the Rental Assistance Program and Housing for Elderly Persons; Advocacy Agenda, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Connecticut Association of Residential Facilities (CARF)/ Connecticut Association of Nonprofits- Newsletters, publications, annual report, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Connecticut Civil Liberties Union (CCLU)-Civil Liberties News- Publications, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Connecticut Coalition of Citizens with Disabilities (CCCD)- PCA option with Medicaid issue- Meeting agendas and minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Connecticut Coalition of Citizens with Disabilities (CCCD)- Correspondence, legislative goals, testimonies, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR)- Retreat schedule and notes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Connecticut Coalition for LGBT Civil Rights (CCLGBTCR)- Email correspondence, Hay,arket Grant Proposal, meeting agendas/notes, articles, events, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Connecticut Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities- "In Pursuit of Justice" Spring, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Public Health- Cryptosporidiosis outbreak and public drinking supplies, speacial report by National Association of People with AIDS "What's on Tap?", 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Connecticut Ethics Commission- Index to Client Lobbyist Code Information, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Connecticut HIV Care Conference- Materials, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Connecticut HIV Prevention Community Planning Group- Meeting agenas and notes., 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Connecticut HIV Prevention Community Planning Group- Meeting agendas, notes, newsletter, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Connecticut Insurance Assistance program for AIDS Patients (CIAPAP), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Connecticut legislation for providing services for persons with HIV/AIDS, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Connecticut National Abortion and Reproduction Action League- Cinco de Mayo Fiesta and Auction Benefit, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Connecticut National Organization of Women (CT NOW)- Campaign to Save Women's Lives packet, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Connecticut Positive Action Coalition- Grant proposal, alerts, By-laws, Request for Proposal, correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Connecticut Positive Action Coalition- HIV+ Leadership Network- Meeting agendas, recommendations sheet, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Connecticut Positive Action Coalition- "Organizational Assessment, Recommendations and Plan", January, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Connecticut Sexual Assault Crisis Services (CONNSACS)- Publications, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Connecticut Union of Disability Action Groups (CUDAG)- Newsletters, alerts, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Connecticut Urban Resources Enterprise (CURE)- Information about organization, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Connecticut Women's Education and Legal Fund (CWEALF)- Workshop, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Connecticut Women's Health Campaign, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Consumer Advocacy Training, New York City, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Continuum Shares Services Program- Contract documents, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Contract with America- Released by Republican group, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Corporation for Supportive Housing- "Supportive Housing in Connecticut: Progress Report of State-Sponsored Initiatives" Powerpoint printout, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Cost of AIDS care- "The $147,000 Misunderstanding; Repercussions of Overestimating the Cost of AIDS" by Jesse Green, Gerald M. Oppenheimer, and Neil Wintfeld, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Deaf Commission/ AIDS Task Force- Correspondence, meeting mintues, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Department of Education, Division of Teaching and Learning- HIV Education update, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Department of Public Health- Correspondence with CAAC, meeting notes, reports., 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Department of Public Health- Managed Care Workgroup, Dasario v. Thomas court case, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Dignity/ Hartford- Board Meeting, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dignity/ Hartford- Board Meeting, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Direct Donor Campaign - Tally Sheets, Phone Scripts, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Direct Donor Campaign - Pearl Lerner Kane Consulting Group- Plans/solutions for challenges faced by CAAC, volunteering opportunities, direct mailings, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Direct Donor Campaign- Mock-Up & Final versions for mailing., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Disability articles, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - DPHAS (Department of Public Health and Addiction Services) Entitlement Grant- Notes, reports, Union Chronicle newsletters, meeting agendas/minutes, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - DPHAS Entitlement Grant - Weiner Report- "Viable Models for Providing Personal Assistance Services to Persons with Disabilities Under Medicaid: An Analysis for the Connecticut Department of Social Services.", August, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Drug Policy Reform- Articles; HIV drug guides, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - DSS (Department of Social Services) Adult Services Programs- Workshop, general information, January, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Equity in Education and Safer Schools: Task Force of True Colors- Meeting notes and newspaper article, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fact Sheets- HIV/AIDS prevention, sex education, condom use, etc., 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Family Care Visiting Nurse and Home Care Agency, LLC- Information packet (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Federal AIDS Programs outline; Federal Appropriation Levels for Federal AIDS programs, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fierstein, Harvey- Printed letter asking for public support of CAAC, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Food & Drug Administration Reform (FDA)- Information from The Patient's Coalition, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Freedom Of Information Act/New Haven Health Department complaint, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Funding Levels- State and Federal reports, correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Funding Sources; Fundraiser Training, tips for sucessful fundraisers, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Gay Marriage- Newspaper articles, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Gay Rights Bill/Military Campus Ban- Notice to contact local politicians, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - GlaxoSmithKline Public Policy and Advocacy-"Policy Briefing: Facts and Figures on Important Pharmaceutical Issues.", 2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Government official correspondence responses to CAAC, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Governor's Race- Questions for candidates & repsonses, forums, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Grassroot Queers- Anti-Christian Right flyers, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Greater Hartford AIDS Consortium (GHAC)- 1992 Grant awarded; Grant #1 Reports (payments), 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Greater Hartford AIDS Consortium- Grant no.1 Application, correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Greater Hartford AIDS Consortium- Grant no. 2 Application, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Greater Hartford AIDS Consortium- Grant no. 2 Reports and Approval, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Greater Hartford AIDS Consortium- Grant no. 3/Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Greater Hartford AIDS Consortium- Grant no. 4 Application/Approval, February, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Greater Hartford HIV Action Initiative- Correspondence, reports, meeting notes, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Greater Hartford HIV Action Initiative- Correspondence, reports, meeting notes, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Greater Hartford HIV Action Initiative- "Initiatives" newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Greater Hartford HIV Action Initiative- Strategic Plan, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Greater New Haven Area Combined Federal Campaign- Members of Local Federation Application from CAAC, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Guardian Update (periodical)- Guardian Health Assocition-One page, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Hartford's Challenges- Written notes, "People for Change", Culture of Peace project, disabilities information in the city (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - "Hartford Children's Health: A Report Card."- Child Council, Inc.; Child Abuse Prevention Campaign, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Hartford Gay and Lesbian Health Collective- Annual Report, brochures, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Hartford Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual Community Action Program- Overview, goals, membership, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hartford Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual Inner City Youth Project- Flyers for events, task force on Hartford GLB youth, fact sheets, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Hartford Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual Inner City Youth Project- Meeting minutes/notes, Grant proposals, fundraising, receipts, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Hartford HIV Program Manager position- City budget cuts, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Hartford Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Community Action Program Pt. 1- Meeting notes, Needs Assessment Questionnaire, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Hartford Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Community Action Program Pt. 2- Meeting notes, organization structure, brochures for various organizations/information, Student project evaluations, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Harvard AIDS Institute- Correspondence, conference materials, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Haymarket Grant- Application, Reports, January, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Haymarket Grant- Application, Reports, Additional Grant, September, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Haymarket People's Fund- Announcement of grant rewards, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Health Resources and Services Administration- "Innovations: Issues in HIV Service Delivery", 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation- Publications List, 1995; 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - HIV/AIDS Consumer Training Agenda- Materials for becoming more involved, outreach (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - HIV/AIDS Policy and Community Organizing Work- Call for funding, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - HIV/AIDS- Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - HIV Drug Adherence Presentation- CT Positive Action Coalition- Script., August 14, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - HIV Frontline- Periodical (REMOVED), 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - HIV in Hartford- Informational Booklet, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - HIV Name Reporting Information- AIDS Surveillance plans- Information, articles, fact sheets, correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - HIV Name Reporting Survey Results, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - HIV Policy Watch- Periodical- San Francisco AIDS Foundation, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - HIV Prevention Education Funding Request- Committee Bill #593, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - HIV Publications Pt. 1- Brochures, pamphlets, booklets, etc. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - HIV Publications Pt. 2- Brochures, pamphlets, booklets, etc. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "How to Lobby" Instructions, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - HRSA- AIDS Education & Training Centers- Participant Information Form, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund- "Votes of the 101st-103rd Congress", 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Human Rights Commission, San Francisco- "Investigation into Discrimination Against Transgendered People", September, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Immigrant/ Migrant HIV/AIDS Assessment, October 1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Independent Living Resources- "A Model for a Consumer Directed Personal Assistance Agency", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Institute for Community Research- "In Action," v.1 no.1 Spring, Hartford, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)